nigeriang.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Nigeria Content Online

**Nigeriang.com Privacy Notice**

**# Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Nigeriang.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How You Can Access Or Correct** **Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by login to http://nigeriang.com . We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, contact us as follows or submit a requests at http://www.nigeriang.com/contact

Address:

Nigeriang.com

Confabee Office  
No 1A Constitution Road  
Kaduna  
Kaduna State  
Nigeria

Telephone: +234(0)62888099 , +234(0)62888098, +234(0)80 3705 2246

http://www.nigeriang.com

Information:

All inquiries can be sent via email( contactus [at] nigeriang.com ) and will receive 24hr service every day of the week. All phone calls and visits to the office should follow this schedule. Customer Service Hours: Monday – Friday 08:00 – 17:00 hrs GMT+1
